bquiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "What feature helps birds fly, keep warm, and attract mates?",
        "choices": ["Feathers", "Scales", "Fur", "Skin"],
        "answer": "Feathers"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do birds hatch their babies?",
        "choices": ["From seeds", "From eggs", "From pouches", "From nests"],
        "answer": "From eggs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do birds live?",
        "choices": ["Only in forests", "Only in deserts", "Only in cities", "Everywhere"],
        "answer": "Everywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "What physical feature do birds have for attracting mates?",
        "choices": ["Fur", "Feathers", "Scales", "Skin"],
        "answer": "Feathers"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of birds' lightweight bones?",
        "choices": ["To swim underwater", "To dig burrows", "To fly easier", "To carry heavy objects"],
        "answer": "To fly easier"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do birds use their beaks or bills for?",
        "choices": ["For hearing", "For smelling", "For eating", "For breathing"],
        "answer": "For eating"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do eagles use their sharp, curved beaks for?",
        "choices": ["Tearing meat", "Cracking nuts", "Sipping nectar", "Building nests"],
        "answer": "Tearing meat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do hummingbirds use their long, slender beaks for?",
        "choices": ["Tearing meat", "Cracking nuts", "Sipping nectar", "Building nests"],
        "answer": "Sipping nectar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What physical feature do birds use for navigating the skies and finding food?",
        "choices": ["Strong legs", "Keen eyesight and strong wings", "Sharp teeth", "Long tails"],
        "answer": "Keen eyesight and strong wings"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do feathers help birds do?",
        "choices": ["Attract mates", "Keep warm", "Fly", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do birds use to build nests?",
        "choices": ["Sticks", "Mud", "Leaves", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do some birds do every year, traveling long distances?",
        "choices": ["Hibernate", "Migrate", "Nest", "Hunt"],
        "answer": "Migrate"
    },


]